A Guide to the Across the Way Productions, Inc., 2002-2016
Radford University, University Archives, McConnell Library
- 6. Live Discs and Other C.D's
  - 6.8 Floyd Fest 9, July 22-25, 2010
    - Alexis P. Sutter Band 1 of 2, 7/24/10 (Volume Binder 3)
    - Alexis P. Sutter Band 2 of 2, 7/24/10 (Volume Binder 3)
    - American Aquarium, 7/23/10 (Volume Binder 3)
    - American Aquarium, 7/24/10 (Volume Binder 3)
    - Atkinsons, 7/24/10 (Volume Binder 3)
    - B.A.S, 2010 (Volume Binder 3)
    - Bassehoa Kayate & Ngoui Ba, 7/24/10 (Volume Binder 3)
    - Bearfoot, 7/24/10 (Volume Binder 3)
    - Bearfoot, 7/25/10 (Volume Binder 3)
    - Big Daddy Love Band, 7/22/10 (Volume Binder 3)
    - Blue Mule, 7/24/10 (Volume Binder 3)
    - Boulder Acoustic Soc., 7/23/10 (Volume Binder 3)
    - Budos Band, 7/23/10 (Volume Binder 3)
    - Cornmeal, 7/22/10 (Volume Binder 3)
    - Cornmeal, 7/23/10 (Volume Binder 3)
    - Diane Durrett, 7/23/10 (Volume Binder 3)
    - Danger Muffin, 7/23/10 (Volume Binder 3)
    - Danger Muffin, 7/24/10 (Volume Binder 3)
    - Danger Muffin, 7/25/10 (Volume Binder 3)
    - Danger Muffin, 2010 (Volume Binder 3)
    - Danny Knicely & Friends, 7/23/10 (Volume Binder 3)
    - Deer Tich, 7/23/10 (Volume Binder 3)
    - Deer Tich, 7/24/10 (Volume Binder 3)
    - Diane Durrett, 7/24/10 (Volume Binder 3)
    - DJ Williams, 2010 (Volume Binder 3)
    - DJ Williams, 7/25/10 (Volume Binder 3)
    - Dot Dot Dash, 7/23/10 (Volume Binder 3)
    - Dot Line Project, 7/23/10 (Volume Binder 3)
    - Dot Line Project, 7/24/10 (Volume Binder 3)
    - Electric Codphice, 2010 (Volume Binder 3)
    - Eric Kresho & Ch 2 1 of 2, 7/22/10 (Volume Binder 3)
    - Eric Kresho & CH 2 2 OF 2, 7/22/10 (Volume Binder 3)
    - Farm Vegas, 7/23/10 (Volume Binder 3)
    - Farm Vegas, 7/23/10 (Volume Binder 3)
    - Farm Use Only part 1 (square dance), 7/24/10 (Volume Binder 3)
    - Farm Use Only part 2 (square dance), 7/24/10 (Volume Binder 3)
    - Farm Vegas, 7/24/10 (Volume Binder 3)
    - Farm Use Only w/ Hoorah, 7/24/10 (Volume Binder 3)
    - Galatic 1 of 2, 7/22/10 (Volume Binder 3)
    - Galatic 2 of 2, 7/22/10 (Volume Binder 3)
    - Goose Creek 1 of 2, 2010 (Volume Binder 3)
    - Goose Creek 2 of 2, 2010 (Volume Binder 3)
    - Hackensaw Boys, 7/24/10 (Volume Binder 3)
    - Hackensaw Boys, 7/25/10 (Volume Binder 3)
    - Holy Ghost Tent Revival, 7/23/10 (Volume Binder 3)
    - Holy Ghost Tent Revival, 7/24/10 (Volume Binder 3)
    - The Hot Seats, 7/23/10 (Volume Binder 3)
    - The Hot Seats (Night), 7/24/10 (Volume Binder 3)
    - Jason Spooner Trio, 7/23/10 (Volume Binder 3)
    - Jason Spooner Trio, 7/24/10 (Volume Binder 3)
    - Jason Spooner Trio, 7/25/10 (Volume Binder 3)
    - JJ Grey & Mafro, 7/24/10 (Volume Binder 3)
    - JP Harris and the Tough Choices, 7/23/10 (Volume Binder 3)
    - JP Harris and the Tough Choices, 7/24/10 (Volume Binder 3)
    - JP Harris and the Tough Choices, 7/25/10 (Volume Binder 3)
    - Joe Pitts Band, 7/23/10 (Volume Binder 3)
    - Joe Pug and the Hundred Mile Band, 7/24/10 (Volume Binder 3)
    - Johnsons X-Roads, 2010 (Volume Binder 3)
    - Kat Mills 1-30, Mitch Brrett 30-60, 7/25/10 (Volume Binder 3)
    - Kat Mills, 7/23/10 (Volume Binder 3)
    - Kat Mills, 7/24/10 (Volume Binder 3)
    - Krista Bell and the Johns, 7/23/10 (Volume Binder 3)
    - Kouono, 7/23/10 (Volume Binder 3)
    - Lefty Williams Band, 2010 (Volume Binder 3)
    - Lefty Williams Band, 7/23/10 (Volume Binder 3)
    - Levou Helen Band 1 of 2, 7/24/10 (Volume Binder 3)
    - Levou Helen Band 2 of 2, 7/24/10 (Volume Binder 3)
    - Lingo, 7/23/10 (Volume Binder 3)
    - Lingo, 7/24/10 (Volume Binder 3)
    - Low Anthem, 7/24/10 (Volume Binder 3)
    - Mantras, 7/22/10 (Volume Binder 3)
    - Mantras, 7/23/10 (Volume Binder 3)
    - Missy Raines and the New Hip, 2010 (Volume Binder 3)
    - Mitch Barrett, 7/24/10 (Volume Binder 3)
    - Mountain Heart, 7/24/10 (Volume Binder 3)
    - Mountain Heart, 7/25/10 (Volume Binder 3)
    - Ms. Tess, 2010 (Volume Binder 3)
    - Ms. Tess and the Bon Ton Parade, 7/24/10 (Volume Binder 3)
    - Mumbles, 7/24/10 (Volume Binder 3)
    - My RADIO, 7/24/10 (Volume Binder 3)
    - Old Crow Medicine Show 1 of 2, 7/24/10 (Volume Binder 3)
    - Old Crow Medicine Show 2 of 2, 7/24/10 (Volume Binder 3)
    - Old Sledge, 7/24/10 (Volume Binder 3)
    - Packway Handle Band, 7/22/10 (Volume Binder 3)
    - Papadorvo, 7/23/10 (Volume Binder 3)
    - Pimps of Joy, 7/23/10 (Volume Binder 3)
    - Possum Jenkins, 7/24/10 (Volume Binder 3)
    - Possum Jenkins, 7/25/10 (Volume Binder 3)
    - Railroad Earth 1 of 2, 7/23/10 (Volume Binder 3)
    - Railroad Earth 2 of 2, 7/23/10 (Volume Binder 3)
    - Ralph Roddenberry, 7/23/10 (Volume Binder 3)
    - Ralph Roddenberry, 7/24/10 (Volume Binder 3)
    - Rising Applachia, 7/22/10 (Volume Binder 3)
    - Rising Appalachia, 7/23/10 (Volume Binder 3)
    - Rising Applachia, 7/24/10 (Volume Binder 3)
    - Robert Jospe, 2010 (Volume Binder 3)
    - Robert Jospe, 7/25/10 (Volume Binder 3)
    - Rockridge Bros., 7/22/10 (Volume Binder 3)
    - The Rootstone Jug Band, 7/24/10 (Volume Binder 3)
    - Rosies Pawn Shop, 7/24/10 (Volume Binder 3)
    - Rosies Pawn Shop, 7/25/10 (Volume Binder 3)
    - Sam Bush 1 of 2, 2010 (Volume Binder 3)
    - Sam Bush 2 of 2, 2010 (Volume Binder 3)
    - SauerKraut, 7/24/10 (Volume Binder 3)
    - Shortwave Society, 7/23/10 (Volume Binder 3)
    - Shortwave Society, 7/24/10 (Volume Binder 3)
    - Solas, 7/25/10 (Volume Binder 3)
    - Soulive, 7/23/10 (Volume Binder 3)
    - Soulive, 7/23/10 (Volume Binder 3)
    - Sol Driven Train, 7/24/10 (Volume Binder 3)
    - Soulhound pt. 1, 7/23/10 (Volume Binder 3)
    - Steele Wheels, 7/25/10 (Volume Binder 3)
    - Tennesse Bolt Smokers, 7/24/10 (Volume Binder 3)
    - Tennesse Bolt Smokes, 7/25/10 (Volume Binder 3)
    - Tift Merritt, 7/25/10 (Volume Binder 3)
    - Travis Elliott, 7/23/10 (Volume Binder 3)
    - Travis Elliot, 7/25/10 (Volume Binder 3)
    - Two Man Gentleman Band, 7/25/10 (Volume Binder 3)
    - Two Man Gentleman Band, 7/25/10 (Volume Binder 3)
    - William Walter & Co., 2010 (Volume Binder 3)
    - William Walter Band, 7/24/10 (Volume Binder 3)
    - The WIYOS, 7/24/10 (Volume Binder 3)
    - The WIYOS, 7/25/10 (Volume Binder 3)
    - The Young Sinclairs, 7/25/10 (Volume Binder 3)
  - 6.9 Floyd Fest X, July 28-31, 2011 (Volume Binder 3)
    - Main Stage, 7/28/11 (Volume Binder 4)
    - Main Stage, 7/29/11 (Volume Binder 4)
    - Main Stage, 7/30/11 (Volume Binder 4)
    - Main Stage, 7/31/11 (Volume Binder 4)
    - Hill Holler, 7/28/11 (Volume Binder 4)
    - Hill Holler, 7/29/11 (Volume Binder 4)
    - Hill Holler, 7/30/11 (Volume Binder 4)
    - Hill Holler, 7/31/11 (Volume Binder 4)
    - Allen Thompson, 2011 (Volume Binder 4)
    - Alliens, 2011 (Volume Binder 4)
    - American Aquarium, 2011 (Volume Binder 4)
    - American Dumpster, 2011 (Volume Binder 4)
    - American Dumpster, 2011 (Volume Binder 4)
    - Atioqui, 7/29/11 (Volume Binder 4)
    - Big Something, 7/28/11 (Volume Binder 4)
    - Big Something, 2011 (Volume Binder 4)
    - Blue Mule, 2011 (Volume Binder 4)
    - Blue Mule, 2011 (Volume Binder 4)
    - The Boatmen, 2011 (Volume Binder 4)
    - The Boatmen, 2011 (Volume Binder 4)
    - The Brand New Life, 2011 (Volume Binder 4)
    - The Brand New Life, 2011 (Volume Binder 4)
    - Brian Elijiah Smith, 2011 (Volume Binder 4)
    - Carolina Choc. Drops, 7/29/11 (Volume Binder 4)
    - Chroma, 7/29/11 (Volume Binder 4)
    - Chroma, 2011 (Volume Binder 4)
    - Copious Jones, 2011 (Volume Binder 4)
    - Copius Jones, 7/29/11 (Volume Binder 4)
    - Dark Water Rising, 2011 (Volume Binder 4)
    - Davin McCoy, 2011 (Volume Binder 4)
    - Davin McCoy, 2011 (Volume Binder 4)
    - DB Rielly, 7/30/11 (Volume Binder 4)
    - Dirk Powell, 7/31/11 (Volume Binder 4)
    - After Dirk Powell, 2011 (Volume Binder 4)
    - Doby, 2011 (Volume Binder 4)
    - Do It To Julia, 2011 (Volume Binder 4)
    - Do It To Julia, 2011 (Volume Binder 4)
    - Donna Hopkins, 2011 (Volume Binder 4)
    - Donna the Buffalo (Night), 7/30/11 (Volume Binder 4)
    - Dot Dot Dash, 2011 (Volume Binder 4)
    - EllaRiot (Night), 7/30/11 (Volume Binder 4)
    - Former Champions, 2011 (Volume Binder 4)
    - Galen Curry, 2011 (Volume Binder 4)
    - Galen Curry, 2011 (Volume Binder 4)
    - Galen Kipar Proj., 2011 (Volume Binder 4)
    - Galen Kipar Proj., 2011 (Volume Binder 4)
    - James Justin, 2011 (Volume Binder 4)
    - Jango Monkey, 2011 (Volume Binder 4)
    - JP Harris and the Tough Choices (Night), 7/29/11 (Volume Binder 4)
    - JP Harris and the Tough Choices, 7/30/11 (Volume Binder 4)
    - Kat Mills, 2011 (Volume Binder 4)
    - Kat Mills, 2011 (Volume Binder 4)
    - Kings of Belmont, 2011 (Volume Binder 4)
    - L Shaped Lot, 2011 (Volume Binder 4)
    - L Shaped Lot, 2011 (Volume Binder 4)
    - The Last Straw, 2011 (Volume Binder 4)
    - L Shaped Lot, 2011 (Volume Binder 4)
    - Lefty Williams, 7/29/11 (Volume Binder 4)
    - Lefty Williams, 7/30/11 (Volume Binder 4)
    - Los Gatos (Thurs), 7/29/11 (Volume Binder 4)
    - Mariana Bell, 2011 (Volume Binder 4)
    - New Monsoon, 2011 (Volume Binder 4)
    - Panel Disc, 7/29/11 (Volume Binder 4)
    - Papadosio 1st Set, 2011 (Volume Binder 4)
    - Papadosio Encore, 2011 (Volume Binder 4)
    - Papadosio, 2011 (Volume Binder 4)
    - Pimps, 2011 (Volume Binder 4)
    - Redstick Ramblers, 7/29/11 (Volume Binder 4)
    - Redstick Ramblers, 7/30/11 (Volume Binder 4)
    - Rev. Peytons Big Damn Band, 7/30/11 (Volume Binder 4)
    - Root of Creation, 2011 (Volume Binder 4)
    - Krumble Bucket, 2011 (Volume Binder 4)
    - Sarah White and the Pearls, 2011 (Volume Binder 4)
    - Shane Pruitt, 2011 (Volume Binder 4)
    - Square Dance, 7/31/11 (Volume Binder 4)
    - Square Dance, 7/31/11 (Volume Binder 4)
    - Tomaque Toma, 2011 (Volume Binder 4)
    - Tomaque Toma, 7/31/11 (Volume Binder 4)
    - Trampeled by Turtles, 2011 (Volume Binder 4)
    - Travis Elliot, 2011 (Volume Binder 4)
    - Turtle Folk, 2011 (Volume Binder 4)
    - Turtle Folk, 2011 (Volume Binder 4)
    - Uncle Mountain 1 of 2, 2011 (Volume Binder 4)
    - Uncle Mountain 2 of 2, 2011 (Volume Binder 4)
    - Watershed Conspiracy, 2011 (Volume Binder 4)
    - Waylon Speed, 2011 (Volume Binder 4)
    - Waylon Speed, 2011 (Volume Binder 4)
    - Wildlife, 7/28/11 (Volume Binder 4)
    - William Walter & Co., 2011 (Volume Binder 4)
    - Yard Dogs, 2011 (Volume Binder 4)
    - Yarn, 2011 (Volume Binder 4)
    - Yarn (Night), 7/30/11 (Volume Binder 4)
  - 6.10 Floyd Fest 11, July 26-29, 2012
    - Big Tony & Trouble Funk, 7/28/12 (Volume Binder 5)
    - Belly Dancers, 7/28/12 (Volume Binder 5)
    - Mighty Wonder, 7/29/12 (Volume Binder 5)
    - March Forth Marching Band 1 of 2, 7/27/12 (Volume Binder 5)
    - Michael Franti, 7/28/12 (Volume Binder 5)
    - March Forth Marching Band 2 of 2, 7/27/12 (Volume Binder 5)
    - Another Roadside Attraction, 7/27/12 (Volume Binder 5)
    - American Dumpster, 7/27/12 (Volume Binder 5)
    - American Dumpster, 7/28/12 (Volume Binder 5)
    - American Aquamarine, 2012 (Volume Binder 5)
    - Art Official, 7/27/12 (Volume Binder 5)
    - Art Official, 2012 (Volume Binder 5)
    - Barefoot Movement, 7/26/12 (Volume Binder 5)
    - Contra Dance with Dot Dot Dash, 7/28/12 (Volume Binder 5)
    - Drew Emmitt, 7/26/12 (Volume Binder 5)
    - Farm Vegas, 7/28/12 (Volume Binder 5)
    - Flour Boards, 7/29/12 (Volume Binder 5)
    - Former Champions, 2012 (Volume Binder 5)
    - Former Champions, 7/28/12 (Volume Binder 5)
    - Garden 1 of 4, 2012 (Volume Binder 5)
    - Garden 2 of 4, 2012 (Volume Binder 5)
    - Garden 3 of 4, 2012 (Volume Binder 5)
    - Garden 4 of 4, 2012 (Volume Binder 5)
    - Glory on the Floor 1 of 2, 7/28/12 (Volume Binder 5)
    - Glory on the Floor 2 of 2, 7/28/12 (Volume Binder 5)
    - Gary Clarke, 7/27/12 (Volume Binder 5)
    - Grass Monkey, 2012 (Volume Binder 5)
    - Gregory Allen, 2012 (Volume Binder 5)
    - Gregory Allen Asimov VIP, 2012 (Volume Binder 5)
    - Gregory Allen Isakav VIP, 2012 (Volume Binder 5)
    - Hoots and Hellmouth, 7/29/12 (Volume Binder 5)
    - Ha Ha Tonka VIP, 2012 (Volume Binder 5)
    - Gregroy Allen Isamov, 7/28/12 (Volume Binder 5)
    - Hot Licks From The Crooked Road, 2012 (Volume Binder 5)
    - Justin Jones, 7/27/12 (Volume Binder 5)
    - Panda, 2012 (Volume Binder 5)
    - Josh Panda & Hot Damm, 2012 (Volume Binder 5)
    - James Justice or Something, 7/28/12 (Volume Binder 5)
    - Kings of Belmont, 2012 (Volume Binder 5)
    - KOB Village - Kings of Belmont, 2012 (Volume Binder 5)
    - Larnell Starkey, 7/29/12 (Volume Binder 5)
    - Leftover Salmon, 7/27/12 (Volume Binder 5)
    - Lizzy Ross, 2012 (Volume Binder 5)
    - Love Cannon, 2012 (Volume Binder 5)
    - L Shaped Lot VIP, 7/28/12 (Volume Binder 5)
    - LOUD, 2012 (Volume Binder 5)
    - Love Cannon VIP, 7/28/12 (Volume Binder 5)
    - Pedrito Martinez, 7/27/12 (Volume Binder 5)
    - Pedrito Martinez, 7/28/12 (Volume Binder 5)
    - Primate Fiasco, 7/28/12 (Volume Binder 5)
    - Ricky + Jerry, 7/29/12 (Volume Binder 5)
    - Orgoue 1 of 2, 2012 (Volume Binder 5)
    - Orgoue 2 of 2, 2012 (Volume Binder 5)
    - Rayna Gellert & Andrew Heller VIP, 2012 (Volume Binder 5)
    - Sam Bush, 7/29/12 (Volume Binder 5)
    - Scott Miller w/ Some Cool Ass Fiddlechick, 7/28/12 (Volume Binder 5)
    - Sweethearts, 7/27/12 (Volume Binder 5)
    - Village 1 of 2, 2012 (Volume Binder 5)
    - Village 2 of 2, 2012 (Volume Binder 5)
    - Whitetop Mt. Band, 2012 (Volume Binder 5)